

I am a digital marketing designer/developer who is proficient with Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma and Sketch. I have extensive experience using e-commerce platforms Mailchimp, Shopify and Amazon Storefronts. I have also recently expanded my skill-set to include HTML, CSS, SASS, JS, React, Redux, Reactstrap and Bootstrap for web development. When working on a project I am completely dedicated and enthusiastic! I'm a great communicator and I enjoy working in a team environment.

# **EXPERIENCE**

DIGITAL DESIGNER - October 2021 - Present 90 Degree by Reflex, New York City

#### ROLES AND RESPONISBILITIES:

- Creating Digital Marketing graphics and assets using Adobe Creative Suite across four online platforms - 90 Degree by Reflex, Yogalicious and Amazon storefronts for both brands.
- Updating bi-weekly promotional banner imagery and website assets and publishing Shopify websites.
- Creating digital assets for Mailchimp email campaigns and promotions.
- Updating and organising Mailchimp email layouts for biweekly campaigns.
- Working with the Web Co-ordinator to schedule email send outs/email promotional content.
- Assisting the Creative Director during Photoshoots for product and lifestyle imagery.
- Maintaining and updating swatch palette library for new products.
- Photo editing lifestyle and product imagery.
- Updating and reviewing promotional catalogue content.

FOUNDER & DESIGNER - 2015-2020 Alicia Seal LLC California, USA

SENIOR PRINT DESIGNER - 2019-2020

Fam Brands, California, USA

PRINT DESIGNER - 2018-2019 Hoffman Fabrics, California, USA

GRAPHIC DESIGNER - 2013-2015

Elegant Clutter, Warwick, UK

GRAPHIC DESIGNER - 2011-2013

Horizon RMS, Ely, UK

TEXTILE DESIGNER - 2006-2008

LI & FUNG, Hong Kong

TEXTILE DESIGNER - 2004-2006 Circle Line Design, London, UK

# **EDUCATION**

FULLSTACK BOOTCAMP 2020 - Nucamp Fullstack Web and Mobile Developement Bootcamp California, USA

BA HONS TEXTILE DESIGN - Chelsea College of Art and Design, University of the Arts, London, UK

### DESIGN & DEVELOPEMENT

Adobe Photohop, Adobe Illustrator, Figma, Sketch Mailchimp, Shopify, Amazon Store Fronts, HTML, CSS SASS, JS, React, Bootstrap, Reactstrap, Github, Mongo DB Atlas.

# **INTERESTS**

I am passionate about art, design and developement and enjoy creating self motivated projects and graphics in my spare time. I also love going to galleries, museums and instillation to keep up to date and inspired by the latest art and culture. I enjoy walking my dog, cycling and learning and speaking other languages such as French.

### CONTACT ME

WEB: www.aliciamorley.com EMAIL: alicia@aliciamorley.com

TEL: 949 522 2509

LINKEDIN: linkedin.com/in/alicia-morley-3ba99532

